qeep.mobi 2019-05-17

# qeep - Chat, Meet, Connect with new People nearby

Data Protection Statement Regarding the Use of Data on Qeep 

Data protection is a matter of trust and your trust matters to Qeep. It is therefore important to us that your personal data is protected and that its collection, processing and use in relation to Qeep's service offering on the http://www.Qeep.de website is compliant with the law. In this document, we want to tell you about how we collect and use data, in order to give you an overview of how your personal data will be used. 

PRIVACY POLICY 

1\. WHO WE ARE 

The Responsible Establishment for the collection, processing and use of your personal data, as defined in the German Federal Data Protection Act („BDSG”), is K2 Interactive GmbH, Venloer Str. 47-53, 50672 Köln („Qeep”). If you would like Qeep to cease collecting, processing or using your data in accordance with the clauses below, whether entirely or with respect to specific measures, you can revoke your consent by email or letter to the following addresses: 

Qeep Support c/o K2 Interactive GmbH  
Venloer Str. 47-53  
50672 Köln  
Germany  
E-Mail: [privacy@qeep.net](mailto:privacy@qeep.net)

2\. WHERE THIS PRIVACY POLICY APPLIES 

This Privacy Policy applies to websites, apps, events and other services operated by Qeep. For simplicity, we refer to all of these as our “services” in this Privacy Policy. To make it extra clear, we’ve added links to this Privacy Policy on all applicable services. 

Some services may require their own unique privacy policy. If a particular service has its own privacy policy, then that policy -- not this Privacy Policy -- applies. 

3\. INFORMATION WE COLLECT 

As we can’t help you develop meaningful, long term and serious connections without some information about you, such as basic profile details and the types of people you’d like to meet. We also collect information generated as you use our services, for example access logs, as well as information from third parties, like when you access our services through a social media account. For additional info we go into more detail below. 

**Information you give us**

You choose to give us certain information when using our services. This includes: 

  * When you create an account, you provide us with at least your login credentials, as well as some basic details necessary for the service to work, such as your gender and date of birth. 
  * When you complete your profile, you can share with us additional information, such as details on your personality, lifestyle, interests and other details about you, as well as content such as photos and videos. To add certain content, like pictures or videos, you may allow us to access your camera or photo album. Some of the information you choose to provide us may be considered “special” or “sensitive” in certain jurisdictions, for example your racial or ethnic origins, sexual orientation and religious beliefs. By choosing to provide this information, you consent to our processing of that information. 
  * When you subscribe to a paid service or make a purchase directly from us (rather than through a platform such as iOS or Android), you provide us or our payment service provider with information, such as your debit or credit card number or other financial information. 
  * When you participate in surveys or focus groups, you give us your insights into our products and services, responses to our questions and testimonials. 
  * When you choose to participate in our promotions, events or contests, we collect the information that you use to register or enter. 
  * If you contact our customer care team, we collect the information you give us during the interaction. Sometimes, we monitor or record these interactions for training purposes and to ensure a high quality of service. 
  * If you ask us to communicate with or otherwise process information of other people (for example, if you ask us to send an email on your behalf to one of your friends), we collect the information about others that you give us in order to complete your request. 
  * Of course, we also process your chats with other users as well as the content you publish, as part of the operation of the services. 

**Information we receive from others**

In addition to the information you provide us directly, we receive information about you from others, including: 

  * Other Users  
Other users may provide information about you as they use our services. For instance, we may collect information about you from other users if they contact us about you. 
  * Social Media  
You may be able to use your social media login (such as Facebook Login) to create and log into your Qeep account. This saves you from having to remember yet another user name and password and allows you to share some information from your social media account with us. 
  * Other Partners  
We may receive info about you from our partners, for instance where Qeep ads are published on a partner’s websites and platforms (in which case they may pass along details on a campaign’s success 

**Information collected when you use our services**

When you use our services, we collect information about which features you’ve used, how you’ve used them and the devices you use to access our services. See below for more details: 

  * Usage Information  
We collect information about your activity on our services, for instance how you use them (e.g., date and time you logged in, features you’ve been using, searches, clicks and pages which have been shown to you, referring webpage address, advertising that you click on) and how you interact with other users (e.g., users you connect and interact with, time and date of your exchanges, number of messages you send and receive). 
  * Device information  
We collect information from and about the device(s) you use to access our services, including: 
    * hardware and software information such as IP address, device ID and type, device-specific and apps settings and characteristics, app crashes, advertising IDs (such as Google’s AAID and Apple's IDFA, both of which are randomly generated numbers that you can reset by going into your device’ settings), browser type, version and language, operating system, time zones, identifiers associated with cookies or other technologies that may uniquely identify your device or browser (e.g., IMEI/UDID and MAC address); 
    * information on your wireless and mobile network connection, like your service provider and signal strength; 
    * information on device sensors such as accelerometers, gyroscopes and compasses. 
  * Other information with your consent  
If you give us permission, we can collect your precise geolocation (latitude and longitude) through various means, depending on the service and device you’re using, including GPS, Bluetooth or Wi-Fi connections. The collection of your geolocation may occur in the background even when you aren’t using the services if the permission you gave us expressly permits such collection. If you decline permission for us to collect your geolocation, we will not collect it.  
Similarly, if you consent, we may collect your photos and videos (for instance, if you want to publish a photo, video or streaming on the services) 

4\. COOKIES AND OTHER SIMILAR DATA COLLECTION TECHNOLOGIES 

We use and may allow others to use cookies and similar technologies (e.g., web beacons, pixels) to recognize you and/or your device(s). You may read informations for more details on why we use them (such as authenticating you, remembering your preferences and settings, analyzing site traffic and trends, delivering and measuring the effectiveness of advertising campaigns, allowing you to use social features) and how you can better control their use, through your browser settings and other tools. 

Some web browsers (including Safari, Internet Explorer, Firefox and Chrome) have a “Do Not Track” (“DNT”) feature that tells a website that a user does not want to have his or her online activity tracked. If a website that responds to a DNT signal receives a DNT signal, the browser can block that website from collecting certain information about the browser’s user. Not all browsers offer a DNT option and DNT signals are not yet uniform. For this reason, many businesses, including Qeep, do not currently respond to DNT signals. 

Generally we only collect personal data where you either supply it yourself when registering a user account or making a transaction or provide it to us when contacting us by email or via the contact form. In these cases, we will use the personal data supplied by you exclusively for forwarding a transaction or a transaction request to our cooperating partners and payment providers or for making contact in accordance with your request.   
Your personal data will only be disclosed or otherwise passed on to third parties if this is necessary for the purpose of forwarding a transaction or a transaction request or if you have previously consented to it. In all cases, we will treat your personal data as strictly confidential and will only pass it to the payment provider subject to compliance with the applicable rules under data protection law. Qeep will not transmit the personal data supplied by you to countries outside the scope of application of Directive 95/46/EU of the European Parliament and of the Council of 24 October 1995 and will only process it in accordance with the applicable data protection legislation unless you expressly consent to its transmission.   
If you set up a User Account with Qeep, the data input by you will be stored and processed by Qeep. Qeep uses this data solely in order to be able to provide you with the functions on the website and in order to improve your user experience on the website and the service offering as a whole. For instance, you have the option to save and track offers. Data on your searches is stored for this purpose. Specifically, the search terms are stored, as is technical information about your device and the browser. The data will only be processed for the functions described and for statistical purposes. It will not be disclosed to third parties unless in connection with the forwarding of a transaction or a transaction request to the relevant provider. 

**Use of your data for marketing purposes**

In addition to processing your data in order to forward a transaction or a transaction request to our cooperating partners and providers, we also use your data in accordance with the paragraphs below in order to communicate with you about our service offering, your searches or other products or marketing campaigns and in order to recommend products or services to you that may be of interest to you.   
You may revoke your consent to the use of your personal data for advertising purposes at any time, without incurring any charges other than the basic communication costs. To do this, it is sufficient to send a message in text form to the contact details (e.g. email, fax or letter) shown in Clause 1. 

**Newsletter**

We use a double opt-in procedure for the sending of our newsletter. This means that we will only email you a newsletter if you have expressly confirmed to us in advance that we should activate the newsletter service. In order to receive the newsletter, you must enter your email in the box provided for this purpose. We will then send you an email notification and ask you to click the link contained in the email to confirm that you would like to receive our newsletter (this is known as a „double opt-in”). If you no longer wish to receive newsletters from us, you can revoke your consent at any time without incurring any charge other than the basic communication costs. To do this, it is sufficient to send a message in text form to the contact details (e.g. email or letter) shown in Clause 1. Naturally, you will also find an unsubscribe link in every newsletter. 

**Email product recommendations**

You will regularly receive product recommendations from us by email. You will receive these product recommendations whether or not you have subscribed to a newsletter. We want to provide you in this way with information about products from our service offering that may be of interest to you on the basis of your recent searches.   
If you no longer wish to receive product recommendations from us, you can revoke your consent at any time without incurring any charge other than the basic communication costs. To do this, it is sufficient to send a message in text form to the contact details (e.g. email, fax or letter) shown in Clause 1. Naturally, you will also find an unsubscribe link in every email. 

**Facebook Connect**

Qeep provides you with the opportunity to log in to our services with your existing Facebook Account (Facebook Connect). If you take advantage of this service, we will only be given access to information about you which you explicitly agree to be disclosed to us. The use of Facebook Connect will not give us any access to further information on your Facebook Profile. The disclosed data will be only used to create a new Qeep user account. No permanent connection between the two accounts (Facebook and Qeep) will be established. Using Facebook Connect, you will be connecting directly with the Facebook-Server, 1601 South California Avenue, Palo Alto, CA 94304, USA. Facebook will receive information about you, using your login credentials with the Qeep services. 

**Cookies**

Qeep uses cookies. Cookies are small text files, typically containing letters and numbers, which are downloaded onto your computer, smartphone or tablet device by websites that you visit. Cookies are widely used to make websites work or operate more efficiently. You can distinguish among so called “Session Cookies”, stored in the working memory (RAM), or so called “Permanent Cookies” stored on the hard drive of your computer. Both of these types of cookies are used to recognize your browser when you access the Qeep services again. We also use cookies in order to improve our services, make our website user friendly, effective and as safe as possible and to give you a better user experience. The following information is gathered, stored and processed through the use of our cookies: anonymized IP address; date of the server inquiry; technical information regarding the OS; and browser and possible plug-ins of your device.   
If you do not wish to enable cookies, you will still be able to browse our website. You can configure your browser so that it does not accept cookies, or so that you will be informed on every occasion a website wishes to store a cookie on your computer. It is also possible to erase any already existing cookies stored by your browser. 

**App & Web Analytics**

This website uses Google Analytics, Firebase Analytics and Google Analytics Remarketing, web analytics services provided by Google Inc, 1600 Amphitheatre Parkway, Mountain View, CA 94043, USA. Google Analytics, Firebase Analytics and Google Analytics Remarketing use cookies, which are text files stored in your computer, to help the website analyze how users use the site. The information generated by the cookies about your use of the website (including your IP address) will be transmitted to and stored by Google on servers in the United States. Since Qeep has activated the IP-anonymization, your IP-address will be anonymized by Google within member states of the European Union or in other states of the European Economic Area. Only in exceptional cases will Google transmit your full IP-address to the USA and anonymize it there. Google will use this information for the purpose of evaluating your use of the website, compiling reports on website activity for website operators and providing other services relating to website activity and internet usage. Google will not combine your IP address with other Google-data. You may refuse the use of cookies by selecting the appropriate settings in your browser, however please note that if you do this you may not be able to use the full functionality of this website. By using this website, you consent to the processing of data about you by Google in the manner and for the purposes set out above. You may choose to prevent Google from gathering and processing the information stored through the use of cookies by downloading and installing the browser plug-in offered under the following link: <https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en>. If you use Qeep on a mobile device, you can use the following link Deactivate Google Analytics , in order to prevent Google from gathering and processing your data through the Qeep Website. If you do so, an Opt-Out-Cookie will be stored on your device. If you delete all cookies on your device, the Opt-Out-Cookie will be erased as well, so that you will have to click on this link again.   
Besides Google Analytics, Qeep also uses ”Google AdWords“. AdWords is used for purposes of Conversion-Tracking, in order to evaluate the effectiveness of certain advertisements and functions on the Website. AdWords also creates and stores a cookie as soon as you click on an advertisement. This cookie is not used for any personal identification, but shall only provide the information where you have visited the same advertisement within a time period of 30 days. You can prevent your browser from storing this cookie by choosing the appropriate settings in your browser software.   
Qeep also uses the Hotjar web analytics service provided by Hotjar Ltd., St Julians STJ 1000, Malta, Europe. The service may record mouse clicks, mouse movements, scrolling activity as well as any text you type in this website, except text in password fields of any randomly selected visits. Hotjar does not collect personally identifiable information that you do not voluntarily enter in this website. It may only collect randomly selected visits (only by storing anonymized IP-addresses). Hotjar does not track your browsing habits across other web sites or text inputted in password fields. The information collected by Hotjar is used in order to improve the Qeep website, make it more user-friendly and monitor that it is performing correctly. Hotjar does not disclose any information to third parties. In case you do not wish any recordings done by Hotjar, you can opt-out from the Hotjar Services for all websites using these services over the following link: <https://www.hotjar.com/opt-out>. Clicking on this link, will store a cookie on your device. In case you delete all cookies from your browser, you will have to click on this link again. 

**Social-Plugins**

Qeep provides you with different Social-Plug-Ins. As soon as you select one of them and click on the particular button, potentially a direct connection with the servers of the particular Social-Media-Provider will be established.   
Our website also uses social plug-ins provided by the social network facebook.com, operated by Facebook Inc., 1601 S. California Avenue, Palo Alto, CA 94304, USA. The plugins are identifiable by a Facebook logo or the notice “Facebook Social Plugin”. When you click on a Facebook button, your browser may establish a direct connection to Facebook servers. Facebook directly transfers the plugin content to your browser which embeds the latter into the website, enabling Facebook to receive information about you having accessed the respective page of our website. Qeep does not give any guarantees regarding the gathering of personal data by Facebook through the Facebook Plug-in. Thus we have no influence on the data gathered by the plug-in and we take no responsibility for the use of this data. For information on the purpose and scope of data collection and possession by Facebook, as well as your rights in this respect and settings options for protecting your privacy, please visit Facebook’s privacy policy: <http://de-de.facebook.com/policy.php>. The embedded plugins provide Facebook with information that you have accessed the corresponding page of our website. If you are logged into Facebook, your visit can be assigned to your Facebook account. If you interact with the plug-ins, for example by clicking “Like”, or entering a comment, the corresponding information is transmitted from your browser directly to Facebook and stored by it. Even if you are not logged into Facebook, there is possibility that the plug-ins transmit your IP-address to Facebook. If you are a Facebook user and do not want Facebook to connect the data concerning your visit to our website with your user data already stored by Facebook, please log off Facebook before entering our website. Further you can block Facebook social plugins by using add-ons for your browser, like the “Facebook Blocker“.   
Our website in addition uses social plug-ins provided by the social network plus.google.com, operated by Google Inc., 1600 Amphitheatre Parkway, Mountain View, CA 94043, United States. The plug-ins are labeled with the Google logo, the Google +1 logo or with the addition “Google Social Plug-in”. When you visit a page of our website that contains such a social plug-in, your browser establishes a direct connection to Google servers. Google directly transfers the plugin content to your browser which embeds the latter into the website, enabling Google to receive information about you having accessed the respective page of our website. If you are logged into Google, your visit can be assigned to your Google account. If you interact with the plug-ins, for example by clicking the “+1” button, or entering a comment, the corresponding information is transmitted from your browser directly to Google and stored by it. For information on the purpose and scope of data collection and procession by Google, as well as your rights in this respect and settings options for protecting your privacy please visit Google’s privacy policy: <https://www.google.com/intl/com/policies/privacy/>. Please note that Qeep does not give any guarantees regarding the gathering of personal data by Google. We also have no influence on the data gathered by the plug-in and take no responsibility for how such data is used. If you do not want Google to connect the data concerning your visit to our website with your member data already stored by Google, please log off Google before entering our website.   
Qeep also provides you with the ability to use the Twitter Plug-in in order to share information you have found on our website. This plug-in is solely provided by Twitter Inc., 795 Folsom St., Suite 600, San Francisco, CA 94107, USA. When you visit a page of our website that contains a social plug-in your browser establishes a direct connection to the servers of Twitter, which is used to retrieve the contents of the plug-in. Through this process, Twitter is aware that you have visited this website. If you are logged in to Twitter while browsing this website, Twitter can match your visit with your account. By interacting with the plug-in, this information is sent directly to Twitter and processed there. If you would like to opt out, please logout of Twitter before visiting this website. For information on the purpose and scope of data collection and procession by Twitter, as well as your rights in this respect and settings options for protecting your privacy please visit Twitter’s privacy policy: <https://twitter.com/privacy>. Qeep does not give any guarantees and has no influence regarding the gathering and processing of personal data by Twitter. 

**Support**

Any kind of support inquiry can be transmitted via our contact form on the Qeep website. For organizing those support inquiries, Qeep uses a ticketing system provided by Help Scout, Inc., 131 Tremont Street, 3rd Floor, Boston, MA 02111-1338, USA. Help Scout processes the information as well as date and time of the inquiry, disclosed by the user via the contact form. Help Scout then submits the information to the Qeep ticketing system. In case you do not wish Help Scout to process your inquiry, please feel free to contact the customer service of Qeep via [info@qeep.net](mailto:info@qeep.net). 

5\. HOW WE USE INFORMATION 

The main reason we use your information is to deliver and improve our services. Additionally, we use your info to help keep you safe and to provide you with advertising that may be of interest to you. Read on for a more detailed explanation of the various reasons we use your information, together with practical examples. 

**To administer your account and provide our services to you**

  * Create and manage your account 
  * Provide you with customer support and respond to your requests 
  * Complete your transactions 
  * Communicate with you about our services, including order management and billing 

**To help you connect with other users**

  * Analyze your profile and that of other users to recommend meaningful connections 
  * Show users’ profiles to one another 

**To ensure a consistent experience across your devices**

  * Link the various devices you use so that you can enjoy a consistent experience of our services on all of them. We do this by linking devices and browser data, such as when you log into your account on different devices or by using partial or full IP address, browser version and similar data about your devices to help identify and link them. 

**To provide new services to you**

  * Register you and display your profile on new features and apps 
  * Administer your account on these new features and apps 

**To serve you relevant offers and ads**

  * Administer sweepstakes, contests, discounts or other offers 
  * Develop, display and track content and advertising tailored to your interests on our services and other sites 
  * Communicate with you by email, phone, social media or mobile device about products or services that we think may interest you 

**To improve our services and develop new ones**

  * Administer focus groups and surveys 
  * Conduct research and analysis of users’ behavior to improve our services and content (for instance, we may decide to change the look and feel or even substantially modify a given feature based on users’ behavior) 
  * Develop new features and services (for example, we may decide to build a new interests-based feature further to requests received from users). 

**To prevent, detect and fight fraud or other illegal or unauthorized activities**

  * Address ongoing or alleged misbehavior on and off-platform 
  * Perform data analysis to better understand and design countermeasures against these activities 
  * Retain data related to fraudulent activities to prevent against recurrences 

**To ensure legal compliance**

  * Comply with legal requirements 
  * Assist law enforcement 
  * Enforce or exercise our rights, for example our Terms 

**To process your information as described above, we rely on the following legal bases:**

  * Provide our service to you: Most of the time, the reason we process your information is to perform the contract that you have with us. For instance, as you go about using our service to build meaningful connections, we use your information to maintain your account and your profile, to make it viewable to other users and recommend other users to you. 
  * Legitimate interests: We may use your information where we have legitimate interests to do so. For instance, we analyze users’ behavior on our services to continuously improve our offerings, we suggest offers we think might interest you, and we process information for administrative, fraud detection and other legal purposes. 
  * Consent: From time to time, we may ask for your consent to use your information for certain specific reasons. You may withdraw your consent at any time by contacting us at the address provided at the end of this Privacy Policy. 

6\. HOW WE SHARE INFORMATION 

As our goal is to help you make serious, meaningful and long term connections, the main sharing of users’ information is, of course, with other users. We also share some users’ information with service providers and partners who assist us in operating the services, in some cases, legal authorities. Read on for more details about how your information is shared with others. 

  * **With other users**  
You share information with other users when you voluntarily disclose information on the service (including your public profile). Please be careful with your information and make sure that the content you share is stuff that you’re comfortable being publically viewable since neither you nor we can control what others do with your information once you share it. 

If you choose to limit the audience for all or part of your profile or for certain content or information about you, then it will be visible according to your settings. 

  * **With our service providers and partners**  
We use third parties to help us operate and improve our services. These third parties assist us with various tasks, including data hosting and maintenance, analytics, customer care, marketing, advertising, payment processing and security operations. 

We may also share information with partners who distribute and assist us in advertising our services. For instance, we may share limited information on you in hashed, non-human readable form to advertising partners. 

We follow a strict vetting process prior to engaging any service provider or working with any partner. All of our service providers and partners must agree to strict confidentiality obligations. 

  * **For corporate transactions**  
We may transfer your information if we are involved, whether in whole or in part, in a merger, sale, acquisition, divestiture, restructuring, reorganization, dissolution, bankruptcy or other change of ownership or control. 

  * **When required by law**  
We may disclose your information if reasonably necessary: (i) to comply with a legal process, such as a court order, subpoena or search warrant, government / law enforcement investigation or other legal requirements; (ii) to assist in the prevention or detection of crime (subject in each case to applicable law); or (iii) to protect the safety of any person. 

  * **To enforce legal rights**  
We may also share information: (i) if disclosure would mitigate our liability in an actual or threatened lawsuit; (ii) as necessary to protect our legal rights and legal rights of our users, business partners or other interested parties; (iii) to enforce our agreements with you; and (iv) to investigate, prevent, or take other action regarding illegal activity, suspected fraud or other wrongdoing. 

  * **With your consent or at your request**  
We may ask for your consent to share your information with third parties. In any such case, we will make it clear why we want to share the information.   
We may use and share non-personal information (meaning information that, by itself, does not identify who you are such as device information, general demographics, general behavioral data, geolocation in de-identified form), as well as personal information in hashed, non-human readable form, under any of the above circumstances. We may also share this information with third parties (notably advertisers) to develop and deliver targeted advertising on our services and on websites or applications of third parties, and to analyze and report on advertising you see. We may combine this information with additional non-personal information or personal information in hashed, non-human readable form collected from other sources. More information on our use of cookies and similar technologies can be found in section 4. 

7\. CROSS-BORDER DATA TRANSFERS 

Sharing of information laid out in Section 6. sometimes involves cross-border data transfers, for instance to the United States of America and other jurisdictions. As an example, where the service allows for users to be located in the European Economic Area (“EEA”), their personal information is transferred to countries outside of the EEA. We use standard contract clauses approved by the European Commission or other suitable safeguard to permit data transfers from the EEA to other countries. Standard contractual clauses are commitments between companies transferring personal data, binding them to protect the privacy and security of your data 

8\. YOUR RIGHTS 

We want you to be in control of your information, so we have provided you with the following tools: 

  * Access / Update tools in the service. Tools and account settings that help you to access, rectify or delete information that you provided to us and that’s associated with your account directly within the service. If you have any question on those tools and settings, please contact our customer care team for help. 
  * Device permissions. Mobile platforms have permission systems for specific types of device data and notifications, such as phone book and location services as well as push notifications. You can change your settings on your device to either consent or oppose the collection of the corresponding information or the display of the corresponding notifications. Of course, if you do that, certain services may lose full functionality. 
  * Deletion. You can delete your account by using the corresponding functionality directly on the service. 

We want you to be aware of your privacy rights. Here are a few key points to remember: 

  * Reviewing your information. Applicable privacy laws may give you the right to review the personal information we keep about you (depending on the jurisdiction, this may be called right of access, right of portability or variations of those terms). You can request a copy of your personal information by putting in such a request. 
  * Updating your information. If you believe that the information we hold about you is inaccurate or that we are no longer entitled to use it and want to request its rectification, deletion or object to its processing, please contact us. 

For your protection and the protection of all of our users, we may ask you to provide proof of identity before we can answer the above requests. 

Keep in mind, we may reject requests for certain reasons, including if the request is unlawful or if it may infringe on trade secrets or intellectual property or the privacy of another user. If you wish to receive information relating to another user, such as a copy of any messages you received from him or her through our service, the other user will have to contact our Privacy Officer to provide their written consent before the information is released. 

Also, we may not be able to accommodate certain requests to object to the processing of personal information, notably where such requests would not allow us to provide our service to you anymore. For instance, we cannot provide our service if we do not have your date of birth. 

  * Uninstall. You can stop all information collection by an app by uninstalling it using the standard uninstall process for your device. If you uninstall the app from your mobile device, the unique identifier associated with your device will continue to be stored. If you re-install the application on the same mobile device, we will be able to re-associate this identifier to your previous transactions and activities. 
  * Accountability. In certain countries, including in the European Union, you have a right to lodge a complaint with the appropriate data protection authority if you have concerns about how we process your personal information. The data protection authority you can lodge a complaint with notably may be that of your habitual residence, where you work or where we are established. 

9\. HOW WE PROTECT YOUR INFORMATION 

We work hard to protect you from unauthorized access to or alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information. As with all technology companies, although we take steps to secure your information, we do not promise, and you should not expect, that your personal information will always remain secure. 

We regularly monitor our systems for possible vulnerabilities and attacks and regularly review our information collection, storage and processing practices to update our physical, technical and organizational security measures. 

We may suspend your use of all or part of the services without notice if we suspect or detect any breach of security. If you believe that your account or information is no longer secure, please notify us immediately. 

10\. HOW LONG WE RETAIN YOUR INFORMATION 

We keep your personal information only as long as we need it for legitimate business purposes (as laid out in section 5) and as permitted by applicable law. To protect the safety and security of our users on and off our services, we implement a safety retention window of three months following account deletion. During this period, account information will be retained although the account will of course not be visible on the services anymore. 

In practice, we delete or anonymize your information upon deletion of your account (following the safety retention window) or after two years of continuous inactivity, unless: 

  1. we must keep it to comply with applicable law (for instance, some “traffic data” is kept for one year to comply with statutory data retention obligations); 
  2. we must keep it to evidence our compliance with applicable law (for instance, records of consents to our Terms, Privacy Policy and other similar consents are kept for five years); 
  3. there is an outstanding issue, claim or dispute requiring us to keep the relevant information until it is resolved; or 
  4. the information must be kept for our legitimate business interests, such as fraud prevention and enhancing users' safety and security. For example, information may need to be kept to prevent a user who was banned for unsafe behavior or security incidents from opening a new account. 

Keep in mind that even though our systems are designed to carry out data deletion processes according to the above guidelines, we cannot promise that all data will be deleted within a specific time frame due to technical constraints. 

11\. CHILDREN’S PRIVACY 

Our services are restricted to users who are 18 years of age or older. We do not permit users under the age of 18 on our platform and we do not knowingly collect personal information from anyone under the age of 18. If you suspect that a user is under the age of 18, please use the reporting mechanism available through the service. 

12\. PRIVACY POLICY CHANGES 

Because we’re always looking for new and innovative ways to help you build meaningful connections, this policy may change over time. We will notify you before any material changes take effect so that you have time to review the changes. 

13\. HOW TO CONTACT US 

If you have questions about this Privacy Policy, here’s how you can reach us:  
Qeep Support c/o K2 Interactive GmbH  
Venloer Str. 47-53  
50672 Köln  
Germany  
E-Mail: [privacy@qeep.net](mailto:privacy@qeep.net)

K2 Interactive GmbH  
Effective Date: May 25, 2018
